The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Above Planet Ran Yun
I must hurry back to the Thunder Celestial Temple !
As long as I return...
You're not escaping !
That damned beast
actually dared to betray me !?
There was
a misunderstanding between us earlier.
Oh ?
A misunderstanding ?
I'm a Thunder Celestial Messenger.
Do you dare touch me !?
Go.
Thunder barrier,
appear !
This man exhausted his origin energy.
Killing him
would be as easy as flipping my hand.
But it would be a shame to waste his Illusory Yin body...
Open the thunder barrier
and I will spare your life.
Xu Mu,
there is no irreconcilable grudge between us.
What exactly
do you want ?
A restriction mark ?
He wants me to acknowledge him as my master ?
How arrogant !
Pure thunder energy...
He's indeed a high-grade material for refining a Celestial Guard.
Follow me.
Barren mountains
Abandoned planet
This damn beast...
I know what you want.
You want me to acknowledge you as my master.
Very well !
But after you imprint the slave restriction,
you must let me leave !
Slave restriction ?
So that's what he thought this was...
Fine.
If you break your promise,
I will use the Thunder Celestial Temple's life-saving spell !
Even if I have to exhaust my entire lifespan,
I will burn everything down with you !
No matter how profound this slave restriction is,
I will be able to break it easily
once I recover some origin energy.
After that, I will return to the Thunder Celestial Temple
and make sure that
he dies without a grave !
An artifact that targets the Origin Soul ?
Xu Mu,
what are you doing !?
To make sure the slave restriction is safe,
I need to temporarily extract your Origin Soul.
Why do you need to extract my Origin Soul
for an ordinary slave restriction !?
Could it be you...
Are you really refining my body into a puppet !?
Bastard,
give me my body back !
10 days later
Silver grade !
Xu Mu,
you tricked me !
You thought you were clever
and assumed it was a slave restriction.
Fine...
Fine !
I admit defeat.
But if my Origin Soul is unwilling,
the puppet will be difficult to control.
At worst,
both my body and my soul
will be destroyed !
You will be my puppet for 3000 years.
After that,
you will be free.
What do you think ?
This sword energy...
Even if I use my lifespan and the life-saving spell,
I wouldn't be able to survive.
The puppet from earlier
was incredibly strong
and looks extremely sturdy as well.
If he refines my physical body,
it should be able to last 3000 years, right ?
The thunder energy of these three has the same origin.
They're perfect for refining a Celestial Guard.
If I do my best to cooperate,
he should be able to successfully refine me.
My Origin Soul
will only survive if he succeeds !
6 months later
This is bad !
It failed...
The Origin Soul dissipated...
Since that's the case,
this Celestial Guard won't be able to use any spells at all.
I thought that with an Illusory Yin body and Thunder Beast essence blood,
it would be enough to refine a mid-grade Celestial Guard.
Looking at it now,
raising a Celestial Guard's grade
is very unlikely.
Oh well...
At least I didn't lose everything.
This body has reached the peak of silver-grade
and is intact.
When my Origin Soul is able to leave my body once again,
I might be able to control it.
A jade from the Thunder Celestial Temple ?
Such a powerful thunder barrier...
Furnace Becomes the World ?
Use your own Dao to create a cauldron,
and refine the world with it.
Unfortunately,
this spell requires too much origin energy.
I can't use it before
I reach Illusory Yin.
Thunder Origin Spell
Absorb origin energy from thunder
and quickly condense it into your own.
It will reduce the time
one stays at the Yin and Yang realms...
It can actually condense the thunder
into origin energy for cultivation !
With the help of this spell,
I will be able to reduce the time
it will take for me to reach the second step.
This Thunder Origin Spell is so powerful
that without a thunder body,
cultivating it
would be the same as digging your grave.
No wonder the Thunder Celestial Temple monopolizes it
and rules the Allheaven Star System.
Now that I have a Thunder Celestial Temple token,
even if a real Thunder Celestial Messenger were to encounter me,
they wouldn't be able to see through me.
He was just a messenger,
but he was incredibly wealthy...
The Thunder Celestial Temple
is truly unfathomable.
With these celestial jades,
Late stage Ascendant
is within reach !
6 months later
Wang Lin's avatar
Late stage Ascendant
My cultivation has stabilized.
It's time to probe the secret of the Moongazer Serpent once more.
The flame metal vein is crucial to completing the Heaven Defying Bead.
Even if it's a bone of the Moongazer Serpent,
I am determined to obtain it.
Planet Yun Xia is actually a sleeping Moongazer Serpent.
If the beast wakes up while I am extracting its bone,
I won't survive.
For this mission to succeed,
I need a huge number of Celestial Ascension Fruits
Planet
Thousand
Illusions
to temporarily paralyze it.
half a month later
I wonder which messenger has graced our humble planet.
The entire Huan Family has failed to welcome you properly,
please forgive our manners.
Head of the Huan Family,
come up.
This voice...
It's him !
Huan Fengshen, Head of the Huan Family,
pays respects to Lord Messenger.
Earlier,
we didn't know your identity
and have offended you.
I hope Lord Messenger can forgive us.
He came this time
to settle the score...
The reason I have come this time,
is to take your Huan Family's Celestial Ascension Fruits.
Lord Messenger,
those Celestial Ascension Fruits
are crucial for our Huan Family to enter
the Thunder Celestial Realm in 100 years !
Shut up !
Lord Messenger,
our Huan Family
is willing to give up our qualification to enter the Thunder Celestial Realm in 100 years
Celestial Ascension Fruits
and offer our Celestial Ascension Fruits
are related to the Thunder Celestial Realm ?
to show our dedication to you, Lord Messenger !
We just want to ask you
to forget our old grudges.
Agreed.
Lord Messenger,
they're all here.
We bid farewell to Lord Messenger !
This Thunder Celestial Messenger identity
is quite useful.
Looks like I can use this as an excuse
in the Northern Domain of Allheaven
to do what I want.
Qian Family's Ancestral Home
Planet Thousand Illusions
Qian Kuizi of the Qian Family,
pays respects to Messenger Xu.
We pay respects to Messenger Xu.
Senior Qian Kuizi,
long time no see.
I don't dare to call myself your Senior,
you flatter me.
I heard that you are looking for Celestial Ascension Fruits.
Our Qian Family has prepared a small gift
that we wish to present to you as a token of our appreciation.
He is well-informed
and is putting on this show...
He really is an old fox.
Lord Messenger, wait a moment.
I humbly ask you
to please show us
your Thunder Celestial Temple token
to let us witness its divine might.
Senior, you don't trust me ?
I wouldn't dare.
In Allheaven,
who doesn't know that there are only 99 Thunder Celestial Messengers ?
Their status
is sky high.
How would I dare to offend one ?
The Thunder Celestial Temple token
can't be counterfeited.
It's been less than 100 years
and he has already reached Late stage Ascendant.
Perhaps...
I should bet on him early.
There's one more thing
that I need to ask Messenger Xu.
Speak.
Thunder Celestial Messengers
all have subordinate families.
If you're willing,
I can promise on my Dao
that when you reach Illusory Yin,
our Qian Family will become your subordinates.
Thunder Celestial Messengers
can actually develop their own affiliated forces ?
If my true identity is exposed, it will backfire on me.
If that happens, I won't be able to protect them
and it would destroy their family.
I can't accept
this karma.
I appreciate
your kind offer.
Let's drop this matter.
It must be because of what happened with Huan Wuqing...
He still holds a grudge against me
and I probed him even more today.
What a pity...
This messenger title
is a bit too grand.
Oh well...
As long as it's useful.
Get the fruits !
6 months later
Starry Sky
Northern Domain
Allheaven Star System
After spending all this time
traveling across the Northern Domain,
I have finally gathered enough.
I took the risk of unlocking 3 of its seals.
Although there was no backlash,
it has developed quite a temper.
Planet Yun Xia...
If this mission succeeds,
I'll use the Moongazer Serpent's bone
to complete the metal element
of the Heaven Defying Bead.
Above Planet Yun Xia
In these 70 years,
it's the eighth attempt !
This time...
I will definitely escape this time !
No !
It's all because of you...
Wang Lin !
If you hadn't come to this Allheaven Star System,
this old man wouldn't have ended up in such a situation !
While Wang Lin is reaching Late stage Ascendant, we got a chapter in the novel about what's happening in the Alliance Star System. The information below will probably be adapted later.
Zi Xin (the woman who absorbed Qian Feng's cultivation) became a concubine of the Blood Ancestor. She investigates an abandonned planet where the Ancient God original body was cultivating. The original body had absorbed the whole planet's energy so it collapses entirely. However, its cultivation is stuck and not able to reach 4-stars without the aura of an adult Ancient God.
On planet Suzaku, deep in the Sea of Devils, in the Land of the Ancient God, Tuo Sens is still plotting.
“Wang Lin, I’m about to be free…”
A person with a monkey on its shoulder walks out of the Chaotic Broken Stars. That person is the Sky Devil Magician, the master of the Six Desires Devil Lord.
“The realm under the Thunder Celestial Realm…” Sky Devil Magician’s body flickered and left planet Suzaku.
On Mount Suzaku, Zhou Ru had just reached Nascent Soul. She's now able to open the bag of holding Wang Lin gave Tie Yan before he left. Inside that bag, there was nothing but a white light that entered her head. Her memories of what happened that Wang Lin had sealed flash before her eyes.
Tears appeared on Zhou Ru’s face, and after a long time, she lowered her head, sat down, and hugged her knees. She couldn’t stop her tears.
“Little White, it turns out Uncle never wanted me to find him…”
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.